http://www.rocc.com/terms_and_privacy.html

Customer Area
Contact Us
Experience... The Difference
HomeSolutionsSocial Housing SoftwareCustomer Satisfaction Resource AllocationRepair ReportingMobile WorkingAsset ManagementManagement ReportingBrochures and ArticlesImplementation & Support ServicesMobile WorkingBusiness BenefitsBrochures And ArticlesImplementation & Support ServicesPredictive AnalyticsImplementation & Support ServicesProcess OptimisationFinancial Process AutomationMailroom AutomationHR Process OptimisationDocument & Content ManagementBusiness IntelligenceBrochures And ArticlesImplementation & Support ServicesInfrastructure OptimisationVirtualised & Cloud ServicesManaged IT ServicesIT Security & ComplianceVirtual & Cloud DesktopsDRAAS & Cloud BackupBrochures and ArticlesImplementation & Support ServicesCustomer StoriesCommunityOur NewsAbout UsOur ExperienceOur ValuesOur Strategic PartnersOur TeamBuy Our SoftwareJoin Our TeamBlogRecent PostsTechnical PostsPopular PostsBlog ArchiveFind Us
Menu
Call Us
Email Us
ROCC Terms and Privacy Conditions
TERMS, CONDITIONS AND PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR WWW.ROCC.COM
We are
ROCC Computers Limited. Registered in England & Wales. Company No: 2691706. Registered Office: Stanford Gate, South Road, Brighton, East Sussex BN1 6SB. VAT Registration No. 209 9698 12
Trade Marks
The ROCC Computers logo is a registered trade mark of ROCC Computers Limited under the Trade Mark Act 1994 and registered under no. 2214615.
Terms of Use
This website ("the Site") is owned and published by ROCC Computers Limited ("the Company"). Use of the Site is subject to these terms of use ("Terms") and to the laws of England and Wales.
By visiting the Site ("Use") all entities ("Users") are deemed to accept the Terms, which may be varied by the Company from time to time without notice and republished on this page.
These Terms only govern your Use of this Site.
Use of the Site creates no legal relationships between Users and the Company other than as specified herein. Whilst the Company aims to maintain the Site to a reasonable standard, errors, omissions and service interruptions may occur and the Company accepts no ongoing obligation or responsibility to operate the Site. Neither the Company nor any of its employees gives any representation or warranty as to the accuracy, veracity, completeness or reliability of any information on the Site nor as to the fitness of the Site for any particular purpose nor as to the safety, fitness for purpose or quality of products or services offered by other organisations whose websites can be visited via the Site.
It is the responsibility of Users to independently verify information obtained from or via the Site. In no circumstances shall the Company or any of its employees be liable for any losses or damages suffered as a result of Use of the Site.
All content on the Site including all imagery and text is protected by copyright and may not be reproduced or appropriated other than as allowed by law in whole or in part in any form or via any medium without advance permission in writing from the Company. Should the Company's intellectual property rights be violated, it reserves the right to pursue whatever actions may be necessary to prevent ongoing violation and to recover costs and damages through legal proceedings.
Use of the Company's Trade Marks or of substantively similar names or phrases including registering them as domain names is prohibited by law. Other Trade Marks referred to on the Site are acknowledged as belonging to their respective owners.
PRIVACY POLICY
At ROCC Computers Ltd we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site.
We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.
Information We Collect
In running and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you:
i.          Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
ii.         Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information.
iii.        Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.
Use of Cookies
Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. We may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer fin order to assist us in improving our website.
We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie.  Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer’s hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever
You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish.  This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer. On 27th May 2011, the EC introduced a directive called Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulation 2011 which requires the owners of websites to get specific approval from the visitor if cookies are deployed.  On visiting our site, you will be asked if you are happy for us to use cookies.  You can easily restrict or block the cookies used by this website through your browser settings. The Help function within your browser will provide detailed instruction of how to change these settings.
You might also want to visit www.aboutcookies.org which provides instructions on how to block cookies on all the major browsers. This site also explains how you can delete cookies that have already been stored on your computer as well as general information about cookies.
You should be aware though that most cookies are harmless and restricting them may impact on the functionality of the websites you visit.
Use of Your Information
We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you.  In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:
i.          To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.
ii.         To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you.
iii.        To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.
If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in.
Where your consent has been provided in advance we may allow selected third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods and services which we believe may interest you.  Where such consent has been provided it can be withdrawn by you at any time.
Storing Your Personal Data
In operating our website it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Union for processing and storing. By providing your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We do our upmost to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure that your data is treated stored securely.
Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, sending such information is entirely at your own risk.
Disclosing Your Information
We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:
i.          In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
ii.         Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
iii.        To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.
Third Party Links
On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.
Access to Information
In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. Please note that we reserve the right to charge a fee of £10 to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information.
Contacting Us
Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy at info@rocc.co.uk or write to us at ROCC Computers Ltd, Stanford Gate, South Road, Brighton BN1 6SB.
Subscribe To Our Newsletter
Get in touch with our team now to subscribe to our newsletter or for more information
Name*
* Please include this!
Phone
* Please include this!
What can we help you with?*
* Please include this!
Email*
* Please include this!
* Correct word required please!
SolutionsSocial Housing SoftwareMobile WorkingPredictive AnalyticsProcess OptimisationInfrastructure OptimisationCustomer StoriesCommunityOur NewsAbout UsOur ExperienceOur ValuesOur Strategic PartnersOur TeamBuy Our SoftwareJoin Our TeamBlogRecent PostsTechnical PostsPopular PostsBlog ArchiveFind Us
ROCC Home
Solutions
About Us
Our News
Find Us
© 2020 ROCC Computers Ltd
Terms & Privacy
Cookies
